igrice-games.com 2015-06-10

# Privacy Policy - IGRICE>>BESPLATNE IGRICE>>Free Online Games

##  Privacy Policy

You require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us: **[Contact](mailto:admin@igrice-games.com)**

At www.igrice-games.com, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by www.igrice-games.com and how it is used.

By using the Services you agree to observe and be bound by this Privacy Policy and you consent to the processing, collection, use and disclosure of your information and data in accordance with its terms. Please do not use the Services if you do not agree to this Privacy Policy.

####  Log Files

Like many other Web sites, www.igrice-games.com makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

####  Cookies and Web Beacons

www.igrice-games.com does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

####  Personal Information

We are strongly committed to protecting your privacy online. therefore igrice-games.com does not request nor collect any personally identifiable information. Your IP address may be used to gather broad demographic information and general visiting paterns.

####  DoubleClick DART Cookie

.:: Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on www.igrice-games.com.  
.:: Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to www.igrice-games.com and other sites on the Internet.  
.:: Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL - http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html  
Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include Google Adsense , cpmstar , for more info about the use of advertisement cookies from Cpx Interactive please visit content network privacy policy at the following URL https://www.cpmstar.com/privacyPolicy.html   
These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on www.igrice-games.com send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

www.igrice-games.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. www.igrice-games.com's privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers' respective websites. 

####  Liability

Our policy is to respond quickly to claims of intellectual property violation. Upon receiving notification in accordance with any related copyright organization or owner, followed by valid proof of ownership Igrice-Games.com will review and if applicable, disable and remove the games in question.

####  Proprietary Rights of the Games

Most of the games published on igrice-games.com are free games, freely available on public domains. Games are submitted or suggested to us by our visitors or their owners/creators. Igrice-Games.com can not confirm if their creators have respected the others intellectual properties or rights. Igrice-Games.com do not claim any ownership of the games or characters, logos and trademarks shown within games. All Trademarks and Copyrights are duly acknowledged as belonging to their lawful owners. Igrice-games.com is not associated, authorized, endorsed by, or in any way officially connected with copyright and trademark owners of the games featured on igrice-games.com.

####  Trademarks, logos and characters

images displayed on Igrice-Games.com are screenshots from the games itself, Igrice-Games.com is not connected, endorsed or affiliated with trademarks, characters or logos shown within the games or their screenshots.

####  External Links

Igrice-Games.com site contains links to other sites. igrice-games.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.  
Igrice-Games.com does not accept any responsibility about the websites which are linking to our website and the outgoing links in the games published at the website.

####  Terms of Use

When visiting igrice-games.com website and/or using its any software, game, you fully agree with it on its "Privacy Policy" and "Terms of Use" conditions. If you do not agree on any of these conditions, you are not allowed to use the website and or its services. Igrice-Games.com has the right to update and modify the policies any time. The visitors always should check the related pages to see updates.

####  Access Restrictions

Igrice-Games.com website is suitable the visitors over 13 year age, the younger visitors are suggested to use its service and games together with their parents.
